<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GeoQuiz</string>
    <string name="app_login_title">Quiz App Login</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="nickname">Nickname</string>
    <string name="create_account">Create Account</string>
    <string name="choose_game_mode">Choose game mode</string>
    <string name="start_the_quiz">Start the quiz</string>
    <string name="easy">Easy</string>
    <string name="hard">Hard</string>
    <string name="nightmare">Nightmare</string>
    <string name="clothing">Clothing</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="sport">Sport</string>

    <string name="easyDesc">This game mode’s name is “Easy,” so your questions won’t be hard. Get ready for a relaxed and fun challenge! Whether you’re a trivia novice or just in the mood for something light, this mode is perfect for you. Test your knowledge, enjoy the game, and see how many points you can score without breaking a sweat. Let’s dive in and make learning fun!</string>
    <string name="hardDesc">This game mode’s name is “Hard,” and it’s not for the faint of heart! Brace yourself for tough questions that will put your knowledge to the ultimate test. Only the sharpest minds will conquer this challenge. Think you’ve got what it takes? Let’s see if you can rise to the occasion and prove you’re a true trivia master. Good luck—you’ll need it!</string>
    <string name="nightmareDesc">This game mode’s name is “Nightmare,” and it’s as terrifyingly tough as it sounds! Prepare to face the most challenging, mind-bending questions that will push your trivia skills to the absolute limit. There’s no room for hesitation—only the brave and brilliant will survive this grueling test. Dare to enter? The nightmare begins now!</string>
    <string name="clothingDesc">This game mode’s name is “Clothing,” and it’s all about style, fabrics, and fashion history! From iconic designers to traditional attire, this mode will test your knowledge of the world of clothing. Whether you’re a fashionista or just looking to learn something new, get ready to unravel the threads of these exciting questions. Let’s see how much you know about what we wear!</string>
    <string name="historyDesc">This game mode’s name is “Clothing,” and it’s all about style, fabrics, and fashion history! From iconic designers to traditional attire, this mode will test your knowledge of the world of clothing. Whether you’re a fashionista or just looking to learn something new, get ready to unravel the threads of these exciting questions. Let’s see how much you know about what we wear!</string>
    <string name="sportDesc">This game mode’s name is “Clothing,” and it’s all about style, fabrics, and fashion history! From iconic designers to traditional attire, this mode will test your knowledge of the world of clothing. Whether you’re a fashionista or just looking to learn something new, get ready to unravel the threads of these exciting questions. Let’s see how much you know about what we wear!</string>

    <string name="your_score">Your score: </string>
    <string name="val_points">points</string>
    <string name="question">Question</string>
    <string name="options">Options</string>
    <string name="correct_answer">Choose the correct answer</string>
    <string name="hint">Hint</string>
    <string name="apply">Apply</string>
    <string name="finish">Finish</string>


</resources>