<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GeoQuiz</string>
    <string name="app_login_title">Quiz App Login</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="nickname">Nickname</string>
    <string name="create_account">Create Account</string>
    <string name="choose_game_mode">Choose game mode</string>
    <string name="start_the_quiz">Start the quiz</string>
    <string name="easy">Easy</string>
    <string name="hard">Hard</string>
    <string name="nightmare">Nightmare</string>
    <string name="clothing">Clothing</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="sport">Sport</string>

    <string name="easyDesc">This game mode is called "Easy," so your questions won\'t be difficult. Carefully examine the image and choose the country that best matches it. Not completely sure? Take a hint! Let’s dive in and make learning fun!</string>
    <string name="hardDesc">This game mode’s name is “Hard,” and it’s not for the faint of heart! Carefully examine the image and choose the country that best matches it. Not completely sure? Take a hint!. Good luck—you’ll need it!</string>
    <string name="nightmareDesc">This game mode’s name is “Nightmare,” and it’s as terrifyingly tough as it sounds! Prepare to face the most challenging, mind-bending questions that will push your trivia skills to the absolute limit. There’s no room for hesitation—only the brave and brilliant will survive this grueling test. Dare to enter? The nightmare begins now!</string>
    <string name="clothingDesc">This game mode’s name is “Clothing,” and it’s all about style, fabrics, and fashion history! From iconic designers to traditional attire, this mode will test your knowledge of the world of clothing. Whether you’re a fashionista or just looking to learn something new, get ready to unravel the threads of these exciting questions. Let’s see how much you know about what we wear!</string>
    <string name="historyDesc">This game mode’s name is “History,” and it’s your ticket to a journey through time! Challenge yourself with questions about ancient civilizations, famous events, legendary leaders, and turning points that shaped our world. Whether you’re a history buff or just curious about the past, this mode will test your knowledge and teach you something new. Let’s see how well you know history!</string>
    <string name="sportDesc">This game mode’s name is “Sport,” and it’s all about athletic achievements, legendary players, and unforgettable moments! From the Olympics to the World Cup, test your knowledge of sports rules, records, and history. Whether you’re a die-hard fan or just enjoy a good game, this mode will keep you on your toes. Are you ready to prove you’re a true sports enthusiast? Game on!</string>

    <string name="your_score">Your score: </string>
    <string name="val_points">points</string>
    <string name="question">Question</string>
    <string name="options">Options</string>
    <string name="choose_correct_answer">Choose the correct answer</string>
    <string name="hint">Hint</string>
    <string name="apply">Apply</string>
    <string name="finish">Finish</string>

    <string name="quiz_results">Quiz Results</string>
    <string name="congratulations">Congratulations!</string>
    <string name="your_score_is">Your score is:</string>
    <string name="number_points">95</string>
    <string name="points">points</string>
    <string name="max_score">max:</string>

    <string name="go_to_quizzes">Go to quizzes</string>
    <string name="help_project">Help project</string>
    <string name="send_content">Send content</string>
    <string name="rate_us">Rate us!</string>
    <string name="userpic_content">Country</string>

    <string name="answer_opt">Country</string>
    <string name="country_name">Country name</string>

    <string name="gallery_permission_needed">Gallery permission needed to pick an image</string>
    <string name="failed_to_get_image">Failed to get image from gallery</string>

    <string name="save">Save</string>
</resources>